seo-friend.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy - SEO Friendly Web Directory

## ES-Solution, SEO Friendly Directories

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us. The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received andcollected and how it is used.

**Log Files**. Like many other Web sites, we makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type ofbrowser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administerthe site, track use’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked toany information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**. This site does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the useraccess or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include: Google Adsense, Clickbank. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on our site send directly to yourbrowsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) mayalso be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising contentthat you see.

This site has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as forinstructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such otheradvertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management withspecific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
